{
    "id": "128_Science_127",
    "claim": "Mexico. - A strong surprise and emotion experience the owner of the social network HI5, Andrew Scott, realizing that overnight the popularity of his page increased a %, to the extent that as it was more than  years ago, it has again become the favorite social network of people in the world. Andrew mentions that with the arrival of Facebook they resigned themselves to the fact that their page would still be forgotten and when it was once the most popular social network in the world:'We were the first viral social network, however people did not like us to allow us to put gifs, songs, videos and endless things that only made the pages treated when someone was logged in. However we remained firm, not even MySpace managed to unblock us, it was until Facebook arrived that we saw our imminent death. It was obvious that we were no longer kings, so we only decided to focus on the country that still appreciated us, which is China and few others, and to take care of that market. It was definitely a very big surprise to realize that from one day to the next we had recovered the billions of visitors we had harshly, it was crazy, we didn't know what was going on ', commented the owner while he was wallowing in his new millions. According to one study, millions of people decided to leave Facebook after the Cambridge Analytica scandal, where their owner Mark Zuckerberg was accused of allowing the sale of private data, a situation that caused people to burst into anger and return to HI5 only for revenge: 'I accept that I did not read the small letters but from there to Zucaritas (sic) selling our data is very different. It's true that I reported until I go to the bathroom and have my profile free for my enemies to see my things and die of envy, but that doesn't mean they have the right to capture what I do to convince us to vote for someone. It's not fair for them to snoop around and see that we like it for forces to force us to vote for Meade, which is the one that comes out the most in my profile ', commented a woman who uploads photos of even the enchiladas she's eating. According to various media, although and everyone knows that hi5 is even less private than Facebook decided to move out of courage towards Facebook:'It was a surprise to open my HI5 account and see pictures of me when I was  years old, nor do I look so changed now that I have , which if it is a little changed is HI5, follow the same way of knowing who visited your profile and since I don't understand it I can't change the privacy to hide everything. I know people can find out more easily about my data in HI5 because they don't have that much security, but at least they don't pretend to protect my information. I've already read the terms of HI5 that are just  lines, and they only mention that they don't have a security system, at least they're sincere ', commented one user. According to several media outlets, the HI5 has even collapsed because among the videos, animations and gifs, plus the arrival of the millions of users who re-entered after years, the page takes between  and  minutes to load, however this does not matter to the users who are willing to do the sacrifice to see Mark sunk for violating their privacy. I'm sorry.",
    "source": "www.elruinaversal.com",
    "date": "11/04/2018",
    "veracity": 0,
    "claims": [
        {
            "claim": "Mexico.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did elruinaversal.com report that Mexico's economy was in decline?",
                    "answer": "11/04/2018"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of the relationship between Mexico and the United States?",
                    "score": 0.6808,
                    "answers": "on 11/04/2018|prep\tthat|mark"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "- A strong surprise and I experience the owner of the social network HI5, Andrew Scott my enemies the owner of the social network HI5, Andrew Scott I realizing that overnight the popularity of my enemies increased a %, to the extent that as his page was more than  years ago, his page has again become the my enemies social network of people in the world.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "How much did the popularity of Andrew Scott's page increase?",
                    "answer": "increased a"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Who is the owner of the social network HI5?",
                    "score": 0.5971,
                    "answers": "www.elruinaversal.com|nsubj\twww.elruinaversal.com reported on 11/04/2018 that - A strong surprise and I experience the owner of the social network HI5 , Andrew Scott my enemies the owner of the social network HI5 , Andrew Scott I realizing that overnight the popularity of my enemies increased a % , to the extent that as his page was more than   years ago , his page has again become the my enemies social network of people in the world|ROOT\ton 11/04/2018|prep\t-|punct\tA|det\tthat - A strong surprise and I experience the owner of the social network HI5 , Andrew Scott my enemies the owner of the social network HI5 , Andrew Scott I realizing that overnight the popularity of my enemies increased a % , to the extent that as his page was more than   years ago , his page has again become the my enemies social network of people in the world|parataxis\tand|cc\tI experience the owner of the social network HI5 , Andrew Scott my enemies the owner of the social network HI5 , Andrew Scott I realizing that overnight the popularity of my enemies increased a % , to the extent that as his page was more than   years ago , his page has again become the my enemies social network of people in the world|conj\tthe|det\tthe owner of the social network HI5 , Andrew Scott my enemies the owner of the social network HI5 , Andrew Scott I|nsubj\tof the social network HI5|prep\tthe|det\tsocial|amod\tthe social network HI5|pobj\t,|punct\tAndrew|compound\tAndrew Scott my enemies the owner of the social network HI5|appos\tmy|poss\tmy enemies|appos\tthe|det\tthe owner of the social network HI5|appos\tof the social network HI5|prep\tthe|det\tsocial|amod\tthe social network HI5|pobj\t,|punct\tAndrew|compound\tthe owner of the social network HI5 , Andrew Scott my enemies the owner of the social network HI5 , Andrew Scott I realizing that overnight the popularity of my enemies increased a % , to the extent that as his page was more than   years ago , his page has again become the my enemies social network of people in the world|ccomp\tovernight|advmod\tthe|det\tthe popularity of my enemies|nsubj\tof my enemies|prep\tmy|poss\tmy enemies|pobj\t,|punct\tthe|det\this|poss\t,|punct\this|poss\tagain|advmod\tthe|det\tmy|poss\tthe my enemies|nmod\tsocial|amod\tthe my enemies social network of people in the world|attr\tpeople in the world|pobj\tin the world|prep\tthe|det\tthe world|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between Andrew Scott and HI5?",
                    "score": 0.594,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tstrong|amod\tI|nsubj\tI|appos\tthat|mark\tthat overnight the popularity of my enemies increased a % , to the extent that as his page was more than   years ago , his page has again become the my enemies social network of people in the world|ccomp\ta|det\ta %|npadvmod\tto the extent that as his page was more than   years ago , his page has again become the my enemies social network of people in the world|prep\tthe extent that as his page was more than   years ago , his page has again become the my enemies social network of people in the world|pobj\tthat|mark\tas|mark\this page|nsubj\tas his page was more than|advcl\tmore|amod\tmore than|prep\tthat as his page was more than   years ago|dep\tyears|npadvmod\tyears ago|advmod\this page|nsubj\thas|aux\t, his page has again become the my enemies social network of people in the world|acl\tof people in the world|prep"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "the owner of the social network HI5, Andrew Scott mentions that with the arrival of Facebook they resigned they to the fact that his page would I network in the world:'We were the first viral social networkhi5 however people did not like they to allow they to put gifs, songs, videos and endless things that only made the pages hi5 when someone was logged I .",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who was the owner of HI5?",
                    "answer": "Andrew Scott"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did the owner of the social network HI5 say about the arrival of Facebook?",
                    "score": 0.689,
                    "answers": "would|aux\tpeople|nsubj\tdid|aux\tnot|neg\tendless|amod\tonly|advmod\tthe pages|nsubj\twhen|advmod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the first viral social networkhi5?",
                    "score": 0.6747,
                    "answers": "with the arrival of Facebook|prep\tthe arrival of Facebook|pobj\tto the fact that his page would I network in the world:'We|prep\tthe fact that his page would I network in the world:'We|pobj\tthat his page would I network in the world:'We|acl\tin the world:'We|prep\tthe world:'We|pobj\twere the first viral social networkhi5|ccomp\tviral|amod\tthe first viral social networkhi5|attr\twere the first viral social networkhi5 however people did not like they to allow they to put gifs , songs , videos and endless things that only made the pages hi5 when someone was logged I|ccomp\tthey to allow they to put gifs , songs , videos and endless things that only made the pages hi5 when someone was logged|ccomp\tthey to put gifs , songs , videos and endless things that only made the pages hi5 when someone was logged|ccomp\tsongs , videos and endless things|conj\tthat only made the pages hi5 when someone was logged|relcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the purpose of the Facebook social networkhi5?",
                    "score": 0.6398,
                    "answers": "gifs , songs , videos and endless things that only made the pages hi5 when someone was logged|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the relationship between Facebook and HI5?",
                    "score": 0.6097,
                    "answers": "when someone was logged|advcl"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "However they remained firm, not even MySpace managed to unblock they , it was until Facebook arrived that hi5 saw imminent death.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "How did hi5 react to hi5's death?",
                    "answer": "not even MySpace managed to unblock they"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did facebook do to block the website?",
                    "score": 0.8027,
                    "answers": "to unblock they|xcomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between facebook and MySpace?",
                    "score": 0.6538,
                    "answers": "not even MySpace|nsubj\tnot even MySpace managed to unblock they|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the cause of death of the hacker?",
                    "score": 0.6402,
                    "answers": "imminent death|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the relationship between Facebook and the website \"hi5\"?",
                    "score": 0.6235,
                    "answers": "that However they remained firm , not even MySpace managed to unblock they , it was until Facebook arrived that hi5 saw imminent death|ccomp"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "It was obvious that they were no longer kingsI so they only decided to focus on the country that still appreciated us, which is China and few others , and to take I of the country that still appreciated us, which is China and few others .",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What country did Elruinaversal focus on?",
                    "answer": "China and few others"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What country did Elruinaversal focus on?",
                    "answer": "China and few others"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What country is China and few others?",
                    "score": 0.6259,
                    "answers": "to focus on the country that still appreciated us , which is China and few others , and to take I of the country that still appreciated us , which is China and few others|xcomp\twhich is China and few others|relcl\twhich is China and few others|relcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the country that still appreciated us?",
                    "score": 0.597,
                    "answers": "to take I of the country that still appreciated us , which is China and few others|conj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "It hi5 definitely a very big surprise to realize that from one day to the next they had recovered I billions of visitors they had hi5 , it was crazy, they didhi5 know what was going hi5 ', commented the owner of the social network HI5, Andrew Scott while the owner of the social network HI5, Andrew Scott was wallowing in new millions.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "How many visitors did Elruinaversal have?",
                    "answer": "they had hi5"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What was the net worth of the owner of the social network HI5?",
                    "score": 0.6556,
                    "answers": "from one day to the next they had recovered I billions of visitors|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many visitors did HI5 receive each day?",
                    "score": 0.6514,
                    "answers": "I billions of visitors|dative\tbillions of visitors|appos\tof visitors|prep\tvisitors|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the name of the network that Andrew Scott owns?",
                    "score": 0.6194,
                    "answers": "what was going hi5|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many people were connected to the social network HI5 in 2018?",
                    "score": 0.5913,
                    "answers": "that from one day to the next they had recovered I billions of visitors they had hi5 , it was crazy , they didhi5 know what was going hi5|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between Andrew Scott and HI5?",
                    "score": 0.5553,
                    "answers": "while the owner of the social network HI5 , Andrew Scott was wallowing in new millions|advcl"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "According to one study, millions of people decided to leave Facebook after the Cambridge Analytica scandal, where owner Mark Zuckerberg was accused of allowing the sale of private data, a situation that caused people to burst into anger and return to the social network HI5 only for revenge: 'the owner of the social network HI5, Andrew Scott accept that the owner of the social network HI5, Andrew Scott did not read the small letters but from there to Zucaritas (sic) selling our data is very different.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What did Andrew Scott do after the Cambridge Analytica scandal?",
                    "answer": "Zucaritas (sic) selling our data is very different"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Did Andrew Scott read small letters?",
                    "score": 0.8263,
                    "answers": "that the owner of the social network HI5 , Andrew Scott did not read the small letters|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did Facebook say about the Cambridge Analytica scandal?",
                    "score": 0.7976,
                    "answers": "private data|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between Facebook and Zucaritas?",
                    "score": 0.6896,
                    "answers": "to Zucaritas ( sic )|prep\tZucaritas ( sic )|pobj\tselling our data|csubj\tfrom there to Zucaritas ( sic ) selling our data is very different|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who is the owner of the social network HI5?",
                    "score": 0.6434,
                    "answers": ",|punct\tthe|det\t,|punct\tthe|det\t,|punct\tand|cc\tto the social network HI5|prep\tthe|det\tsocial|amod\tthe social network HI5|pobj\t'|punct\tthe|det\tthe owner of the social network HI5 , Andrew Scott|nsubj\tof the social network HI5|prep\tthe|det\tsocial|amod\tthe social network HI5|pobj\t,|punct\tAndrew|compound\tthe|det\tthe owner of the social network HI5 , Andrew Scott|nsubj\tof the social network HI5|prep\tthe|det\tsocial|amod\tthe social network HI5|pobj\t,|punct\tAndrew|compound\tthe|det\tbut|cc\tsic|appos\t)|punct"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "It's true that I reported until I go to the bathroom and have my profile free for my enemies to see my things and die of envy, but that doesn't mean they have the right to capture what I do to convince us to vote for someone.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Does it mean that they have the right to capture what I do?",
                    "answer": "they have the right to capture what I do to convince us to vote for someone"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of Trump's political affiliation?",
                    "score": 0.6751,
                    "answers": "11/04/2018|pobj\tmy|poss\tmy|poss\tmy enemies|nsubj\tmy|poss"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does it mean to vote for someone?",
                    "score": 0.6469,
                    "answers": "for|mark\tfor someone|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the name of the website that reported that Trump was trapped in a bathroom and then convinced voters to vote for him?",
                    "score": 0.6297,
                    "answers": "that I reported|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the right to capture what you do to convince people to vote?",
                    "score": 0.5709,
                    "answers": "to convince us to vote for someone|advcl"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "It's not fair for them to snoop around and see that we like it for forces to force us to vote for Meade, which is the one that comes out the most in my profile ', commented a woman who uploads photos of even the enchiladas she's eating.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Where does Meade come out the most in the polls?",
                    "answer": "profile"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What forces are trying to snoop around and see who votes for Meade?",
                    "score": 0.8136,
                    "answers": "for them to snoop around and see that we like it for forces to force us to vote for Meade , which is the one that comes out the most in my profile|advcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does it mean to vote for Meade?",
                    "score": 0.8017,
                    "answers": "for|mark\tfor|mark"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many Enchiladas does Meade eat?",
                    "score": 0.7987,
                    "answers": "photos of even the enchiladas she 's eating|dobj\teven the enchiladas she 's eating|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who uploaded photos of even the enchiladas she eats?",
                    "score": 0.7342,
                    "answers": "who uploads photos of even the enchiladas she 's eating|relcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of Meade's voting record?",
                    "score": 0.7004,
                    "answers": "www.elruinaversal.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "According to various media, although and everyone knows that hi5 is even less private than Facebook decided to move out of courage towards Facebook:'It was a surprise to open my HI5 account and see pictures of me when I was  years old, nor do I look so changed now that I have , which if it is a little changed is HI5, follow the same way of knowing who visited your profile and since I don't understand it I can't change the privacy to hide everything.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Why did hi5 decide to move out of courage towards Facebook?",
                    "answer": "since I don't understand it I can't change the privacy to hide everything"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the purpose of Facebook using HI5?",
                    "score": 0.6352,
                    "answers": "since I do n't understand it I ca n't change the privacy to hide everything|conj\tto hide everything|advcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between Facebook and HI5?",
                    "score": 0.5959,
                    "answers": "www.elruinaversal.com|nsubj\twww.elruinaversal.com reported on 11/04/2018 that According to various media , although and everyone knows that hi5 is even less private than Facebook decided to move out of courage towards Facebook:'It was a surprise to open my HI5 account and see pictures of me when I was   years old , nor do I look so changed now that I have , which if it is a little changed is HI5 , follow the same way of knowing who visited your profile and since I do n't understand it I ca n't change the privacy to hide everything|ROOT\ton 11/04/2018|prep\tthat|mark\tAccording to various media|prep\tto various media|prep\tvarious|amod\tvarious media|pobj\t, although and everyone knows that hi5 is even less private than Facebook decided to move out of courage towards|punct\talthough|nmod\tand|cc\talthough and everyone|nsubj\talthough and everyone knows that hi5 is even less private than Facebook decided to move out of courage towards|prep\tthat|mark\tthat hi5 is even less private than Facebook decided to move out of courage towards|ccomp\teven|advmod\teven less|advmod\teven less private than Facebook decided to move out of courage towards|acomp\tthan|mark\tthan Facebook decided to move out of courage towards|advcl\tto|aux\tto move out of courage towards|xcomp\tout of courage|prep\tof courage|prep\tcourage|pobj\ttowards|prep\tFacebook:'It|nsubj\tthat According to various media , although and everyone knows that hi5 is even less private than Facebook decided to move out of courage towards Facebook:'It was a surprise to open my HI5 account and see pictures of me when I was|ccomp\ta|det\ta surprise|attr\tto|aux\tto open my HI5 account and see pictures of me when I was|xcomp\tmy|poss\tmy HI5 account|dobj\tand|cc\tsee pictures of me when I was|conj\tpictures of me|dobj\tof me|prep\tme|pobj\twhen|advmod\tI|nsubj\twhen I was|advcl\t  years old|dep\tyears|npadvmod\tyears old|acomp\t,|punct\tnor|cc\tdo|aux\tI|nsubj\tdo I look so changed now that I have , which if it is a little changed is HI5 , follow the same way of knowing who visited your profile|conj\tso|advmod\tso changed|acomp\tnow that I have|advmod\tthat|dobj\tI|nsubj\tthat I have|ccomp\t,|punct\twhich|nsubj\tif|mark\tit|nsubj\tif it is a little changed|advcl\ta|det\ta little|npadvmod\ta little changed|acomp\twhich if it is a little changed is HI5|parataxis\t,|punct\t, follow the same way of knowing who visited your profile|dep\tthe|det\tsame|amod\tthe same way of knowing who visited your profile|dobj\tof knowing who visited your profile|prep\tknowing who visited your profile|pcomp\twho|nsubj\twho visited your profile|ccomp\tyour|poss\tyour profile|dobj\tand|cc\tsince|mark\tI|nsubj\tdo|aux\tn't|neg\tsince I do n't understand it|advcl\tit|dobj\tI|nsubj\tca|aux\tn't|neg\tthe|det\tthe privacy|dobj\tto|aux\teverything|dobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "I know people can find out more easily about my data in HI5 because they don't have that much security, but at least they don't pretend to protect my information.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who reported on 11/04/2018 that I know people can find out more easily about my data in HI5?",
                    "answer": "www.elruinaversal.com"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How can people find out more easily about my data in HI5?",
                    "score": 0.8434,
                    "answers": "I|nsubj\tpeople|nsubj\tmy|poss\tat|advmod\tmy|poss"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does it mean to know about your data in HI5?",
                    "score": 0.766,
                    "answers": "because they do n't have that much security|advcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the security requirements for finding out about a person's data in HI5?",
                    "score": 0.7633,
                    "answers": "on 11/04/2018|prep\tthat much security|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the purpose of HI5?",
                    "score": 0.6591,
                    "answers": "at least they do n't pretend to protect my information|conj\tto protect my information|xcomp"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "I've already read the terms of HI5 that are just  lines, and they only mention that they don't have a security system, at least they're sincere ', commented one user.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What did one user say about the terms of HI5?",
                    "answer": "sincere"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What are the terms of HI5?",
                    "score": 0.6443,
                    "answers": "www.elruinaversal.com|nsubj\twww.elruinaversal.com reported on 11/04/2018 that I 've already read the terms of HI5 that are just   lines , and they only mention that they do n't have a security system , at least they 're sincere|ccomp\ton 11/04/2018|prep\tthat|mark\tI|nsubj\t've|aux\talready|advmod\tI 've already read the terms of HI5 that are just|ccomp\tthe|det\tthe terms of HI5 that are just|dobj\tof HI5|prep\tthat|nsubj\tthat are just|relcl\tjust|advmod\tthat I 've already read the terms of HI5 that are just   lines , and they only mention that they do n't have a security system , at least they 're sincere|dep\tlines , and they only mention that they do n't have a security system , at least they 're sincere|attr\t,|punct\tand|cc\tthey|nsubj\tonly|advmod\tthey only mention that they do n't have a security system|ccomp\tthat|mark\tthey|nsubj\tdo|aux\tn't|neg\tthat they do n't have a security system|ccomp\ta|det\tsecurity|compound\ta security system|dobj\t,|punct\tat|advmod\tat least|advmod\tthey|nsubj\tthey only mention that they do n't have a security system , at least they 're sincere|conj\tsincere|acomp\t'|punct\t,|punct\twww.elruinaversal.com reported on 11/04/2018 that I 've already read the terms of HI5 that are just   lines , and they only mention that they do n't have a security system , at least they 're sincere ' , commented one user|ROOT\tone user|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "According to several media outlets, the HI5 has even collapsed because among the videos, animations and gifs, plus the arrival of the millions of users who re-entered after years, the page takes between  and  minutes to load, however this does not matter to the users who are willing to do the sacrifice to see Mark sunk for violating their privacy.",
            "question_answers": [],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How long did it take to load the HI5 video?",
                    "score": 0.6871,
                    "answers": "the sacrifice|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many users were able to see Mark sunk for violating privacy?",
                    "score": 0.622,
                    "answers": "to the users who are willing to do the sacrifice to see Mark sunk for violating their privacy|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the purpose of the HI5 program?",
                    "score": 0.5672,
                    "answers": "who are willing to do the sacrifice to see Mark sunk for violating their privacy|relcl\twilling to do the sacrifice to see Mark sunk for violating their privacy|acomp"
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}